翻译: 奶啾
THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
翻译: 橙砸
翻译: Graaace
翻译: 渡渡
翻译: Ciaran
翻译: 宇宙万宝路
翻译: 海顿
翻译: 豆
时间轴: Heiforn
时间轴: 阿布
特效: 雨人
后期&压制: Jason肖
校对:渡渡
校对：宇宙万宝路
继承
第一季第８集
"布拉格"
监制: 宇宙万宝路
这里景色不错 对吧
It's a pretty great view, huh?
我是指外面的景色 不是我
I mean, out there. Not me.
我们谈到哪儿了 鲍勃
Where are we at, Bob?
不好意思 我... 我根本没听
Excuse me, I... I'm actually not even here.
-你报价5.3亿  -没错
- You're at 5.3? - Correct.
我觉得我们可以接受
And I think we can live with that.
是吗
Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
这个价格很公道
It's a fair price.
我可说不准
Well, I don't know about that.
你将拥有七十家本地电视台
You'll have 70 local TV stations.
买入桑迪 你就是本地的电视一霸
Buy in Sandy, you're King Kong of local.
这孩子知道 他挺聪明
The kid knows. The kid's smart.
谈得通吗
Are we good?
给我们五分钟
Give us five minutes.
我们会另给你们安排房间
We'll set you up with a room.
还可以 对吧 来杯酒庆祝一下
Good, right? Is it whiskey time?
你他妈的闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
-这价格不错  -这他妈的什么事
- Uh, it's a good price. - What the fuck's going on?
他居然把我想要的东西 以合理价格卖给我
He's selling me things I want at a fair price?
那接下来要干嘛 口交吗
So what's next? Fellatio?
我认为他只是想尽快出手
I think he just wants out, fast.
如果真是这样 咱就搞他
If he does, we fuck him.
我觉得咱们已经搞过他了
I think we did just fuck him.
他在微笑
He's smiling.
笑就准没好事
It's no good if he's smiling.
你看 客观地讲
Well, objectively,
如果我们拿到想要的
I mean, if we get what we want
他也拿到他想要的...
and he gets what he wants...
你干翻他们
You screw them out.
敲诈他们
You chisel them out.
狠狠地中伤他们
You fuckin' hurt them.
然后看着他们惨叫
And then you watch them squeal.
我和下一位同志都喜欢伤害人类
I like hurting human beings as much as the next guy,
但是 爸 这他妈已经很好了
but, Dad, this is really fucking good.
送他上电梯 告诉他报价改到4.9亿
Walk him to the elevator and tell him 4.9.
老爸 别啊 这... 这也太侮辱人了
Oh, Dad, no, that's... it's insulting.
送他上电梯 告诉他报价改到4.9亿
Walk him to the elevator and tell him 4.9.
格丽 你去做
Gerri, you do it.
你 滚边去
You, fuck off.
做不了 你就滚蛋
If you can't do it, fuck off!
好吧
All right.
只知道敲手机屏幕 你个怂包
Just text on your phone, ya bendy fuck.
让墙壁暖和起来
Really just warms the walls.
-格雷格  -你好
- Greg.  - Hey.
疼啊 兄弟
Ow! Dude.
等会儿 等会儿 等会儿
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
你还好吗
Are you OK?
怎么了 那个啊 算不了什么
What? Oh, that? That was nothing.
有的时候就得装孙子 你懂吗
Sometimes you gotta play possum, ya know?
让他拿你出气直到没劲了
Let him punch it out till he gets tired,
然后你就出马一举拿下
and then you go in for the kill.
行了 很好 听着 等一下
Right, nice. Listen, hold on.
-怎么了  -肯德尔怎么样了
- Yeah.  - How's Kendall doin'?
他也拿你出气了吗
He's blowing you off too?
我上回见他 他还在和小流氓一起吸毒
Last time I saw him he was smoking crank with some mole men,
但那是一个月以前了
but that was like a month ago.
-他在强撑  -是的 没错 在搞风投吗
- He's hustlin'.  - Yeah, right. VCing?
我这周末也许能见到他 如果他出现的话
I may be seeing him this weekend. If he shows.
-真的吗  -我操
- Oh, yeah?  - Aw, fuck.
伙计 你不会碰巧认识布拉格的毒贩吧
Dude, I don't suppose you know a coke dealer in Prague, do you?
可能认识 怎么了
Ah, probably. Yeah. Why?
汤姆·威姆士丹的单身派对
Tom Wams' bachelor party.
"如果他不出现... " 我可没时间搞这个
"And if he doesn't show..." I don't have time for this.
我给你出个主意 伙计 去他妈的布拉格
Hey, let me tell you something, dude. Fuck Prague.
我女友和她那群傻逼狗崽子
My girlfriend and her fuckin' freak dogs
搞了那种... 你听说过那种派对吗 菱形派对
run these... You ever heard of these parties, Rhomboid?
不会吧
Bullshit.
真的 我牛逼得很
I'm tellin' ya. I'm fuckin' cool.
你看不出来罢了
You don't understand.
怎么 就因为你打了乳钉
Why, because you have a nipple ring
还乐此不疲地大肆宣扬吗
and simply will not stop going on about it?
总比告诉大家你疯狂迷恋德瑞要强
It's better than telling everyone you're down with Dre
就因为他圣诞节给你寄谷物棒
because he sends you cereal bars at Christmas.
死开 我名声在外
Fuck you. I have a reputation.
不可能带我的伙计们去看搞艺术的
I can't take my crew to watch some art pricks
傻逼戴着圆顶礼帽 捻着过时的胡须
dance around in fucking bowler hats and twizzle their mustaches
跟节奏手舞足蹈
out of time to the beats.
说完了吗 你知道还有谁会到场吗
Are you done? You know who else will be there?
桑迪·弗尼斯
Sandy Furness.
放屁吧
Fuck off.
我说真的
I'm tellin' you.
恶心 他还会去那种场合
Bleahh. He goes to that kind of thing?
谁说不是呢 但他正坐在
I know, right? But he is sitting
你父亲梦想交易的另一边
on the other half of your dad's dream deal.
又五十家地方台
Packet of 50 more local stations.
来参加派对 劝服他卖掉
Come to the party, get him to sell,
相信我说的话
and trust me when I say this,
你就会成为皇太子的
you will become the number one son.
桑迪... 会去 我的天
Sandy... goes? Jesus.
没错 把派对名单给我 我帮你们预约
Yeah. Get me those names and I'll get you on that list.
另外 带上肯德尔 好吗
And one more thing, bring Kendall, OK?
我得跟他和好
I need to patch things up with him.
真他妈好
Oh, fuck yeah.
-你觉得呢  -好看
- What do you think?  - Yeah.
伙计 你能把背景低音调大一点吗
Hey, bro, can you turn up the bass in the back?
再大声点
Louder.
-你感觉怎么样  -啥
- You feelin' good?  - What?
-你还好吗  -当然 好得很
- You're good?  - Yeah, I'm great.
激动坏了
I'm psyched.
-好看又随意 对吧 弗兰克  -是
- Nice and loose, yeah, Frank?  - Yeah.
进去的时候
Try not to drag yourself in there
尽量别一副老古董模样
like the world's oldest man.
我会努力的
I'll try.
弗兰克 肯德尔
Frank. Kendall.
-欢迎来达斯特[灰尘]  -你好 伙计
- This is Dust.  - Hey, man.
你好 很高兴联系到你
Hey. Great to connect.
我喜欢这名字 顺便说一句 非常... 嬉皮
Love the name, by the way. Very... funky.
抱歉 请别在意这个傻逼波普爵士舰长
Sorry, please excuse Captain fuckin' Be-Bop here.
波普爵士: 始于四十年代早期极富革命性的爵士乐
最近怎么样
Hey, how's it goin'?
耳环很酷 很有包豪斯风格
Cool earrings. Very Bauhaus.
包豪斯: 德国魏玛市的现代设计学院
我很崇拜你们的作品
Big fan of what you guys do.
辣酱真他妈棒
Fuckin' sweet chili sauce.
谢谢 彼此彼此
Thanks. Uh, likewise.
安吉拉 你带我们浏览一下融资稿怎么样
Angela, you want to spin us through the pitch deck?
-当然了 那...  -不用麻烦了
- Sure. So...  - That's OK.
不用跟我讲融资的事了
I don't need to hear the pitch.
我浏览过稿子 基本明白了
I've been through the deck, and I get it.
情况大概就是
Basically, you buy a
你们从住地下室的某个艺术生那里买画
painting from some art student in a basement,
抬高价格 卖给类似摩根士丹利的情色业务
jack up the price, sell it to some Morgan Stanley sex pest,
摩根士丹利: 全球领先的国际性金融服务公司
然后你 我和那学生都成了大款 是吧
and you, me, and the student all get rich. Right?
我们致力于提升年轻艺术家的影响力
We're interested in increasing the reach of young artists.
以及艺术的民主化
And the democratization of art.
那当然 我明白
No, absolutely. I get it.
你们给边缘人才提供平台
You're providing a platform to marginalized talent,
下一代的艺术家
the next generation of artists.
我就是告诉你们
I'm just telling you how
面对勒索者[鲨鱼]时 外界怎么运作
it works from the outside, to the sharks.
也许我们可以谈谈资金周期
Maybe we can talk about funding cycles.
当然 我们做了个计划
Sure. We've worked out a plan
用于启动后的第一年...
for the first year after the launch...
抱歉 我能说一句吗
I'm sorry. Can I just say something?
那个 我... 我... 我...
so, I... I... I...
我在来的路上...
I got these sneakers...
买了这双运动鞋 因为
on the way down here because, uh,
我想... 我不知道我怎么想的
I thought... I don't know what I thought,
我以为你们都会穿成他妈的比约克[冰岛女歌手]那样
I thought you'd all be dressed like fuckin' Bjork,
而我想留下个好印象
and I wanted to, uh, make an impression.
我就是个蠢货
Um, so, I'm a jackass, um,
事实上 我对艺术一无所知
the truth is, I don't know anything about art.
我知道的是 怎么将你们的概念变成钱
What I do know is how to monetize your concept
然后扩大到理所应当的规模
and achieve the scale it deserves.
别把你的灵魂卖给巨头
Don't sell your soul to some monolith.
我们是精品店 我们脚踏实地
We're boutique, we're light on our feet,
我们不是四人帮 而是他妈的义军同盟[出自星战]
we're not the Gang of Four, we're the fuckin' Rebel Alliance.
四人帮: 英国著名后朋乐队
我是个好人 还了解那些坏人
I'm a good guy, who knows the bad guys,
我有人脉 我会为你们奋战每一天
I've got reach, and I will fight for you every fuckin' day.
我就是能成为你们的沃霍尔的那个混蛋
I'm the asshole who can be your Warhol.
安迪·沃霍尔: 美国著名艺术家 印刷家 电影摄影师
而且... 我刚刚想到
And, uh... yeah, I just thought of that,
显然我还是了解一点艺术的
so apparently I do know a little bit about art.
那... 什么
So... what?
说话啊 我要做什么
Talk to me. What do I need to do?
要脱下我的呆逼运动鞋吗
Do I need to take off my dopey sneakers?
-不用  -我会的 说真的
- No. - I will. Seriously,
我现在就他妈把它们扔出窗外
I'll throw them out the fuckin' window right now.
-它们还不赖  -我要脱了
- They're not bad. - I'm taking 'em off.
-拿着 伊尔汗 给你了  -我买了
- Here. Ilhan, have 'em. - I'll trade you.
行了吗
OK?
咱们能谈了吗
Can we talk now?
我靠
Oh, shit.
抱... 歉
Sor... Um, so,
你觉得... 女士
what do you think... Miss?
在... 你知道...
Uh, betw... You know...
抱歉 我... 我...
Sorry, I... I'm...
我现在进退两难
I'm somewhat between the devil and the deep blue sea here,
因为我楼下的老板在等着我
because my boss downstairs is waiting,
而我楼上的老板又是他
and my boss upstairs is him, you know,
我已经在这待了三个半小时了
so I've been here three and a half hours.
你怎么想 你觉得...
What do you think? What do you...
你要...
Do you want...
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
我让他进去
I'll send him in.
谢谢你
Thank you.
终于
At long last.
这个转轮 在... 转
It's the wheel, it's... doin' its thing.
是的 在缓冲呢
Oh, yeah. It's buffering.
可以试试调低... 低清晰度
You could try knocking it down to low... low quality?
你来吧
Hmm. Go ahead.
就...
Yeah, just...
您... 的头发挺好啊
It's a... heckuva good head of hair on ya there.
我觉得是您母系这边遗传下来的...
I think it's the maternal side that it's carried on, so...
我听说你们
So I hear you and the boys
要去汤姆的单身派对
are heading out for Tom's bachelor party.
是的 是这样的
Yes. That's correct.
罗曼在筹备 可能要去布拉格
Roman's arranging, Prague has been mentioned.
我能告诉你这些
I will tell you this much.
我相信洛根·罗伊对我们的文化有致命影响
I believe Logan Roy is a pernicious influence on our culture.
伊维斯议员: "韦斯达公司是蚕食美国的癌症"
老实说 他就是
He is, to be frank,
-天 真是个... 混... 混蛋  -美国价值观的诟病
- Man, what... a jack...jackhole. - a cancer to American values.
这些话是我慎重说出的...
I don't take these words lightly...
好吧 他失去了我这一票
Yeah, well, he just lost my vote.
听我说
Uh, listen to me.
帮我个忙
Um... do me a favor.
你能确保肯德尔不会被装在盒子里带回来吗
Can you make sure that Kendall doesn't come back in a box?
-好的  -那好 我...
- OK. - Yeah, I...
我不想看他死在
I don't want him showing up dead
什么法国男同的泳池底
at the bottom of some French fag's pool.
不 当然不 我们都不想
Oh, no, absolutely. None of us do.
帮我看着他点
Keep an eye on him for me.
你能帮我做好这事吗
Is this something you can do for me?
我听说他一直
I hear he's been, uh,
在馋嘴
wetting his beak.
好 先生
Yes, sir.
这么说来
Um, in which case,
您现在方便跟我
would now be a convenient time
就我在公司里的职位
to talk with you about, like, a lateral shift
谈谈横向调动吗
in terms of my position at the company?
因为我想离开公园项目
Because I'd like to move on from Parks
去做电子之类的
and into, for example, Digital?
我不想提到谁的名字 因为...
I don't want to mention any names, because I...
可那里的氛围
But the culture there,
有时候有点像人身攻击了
it borders on the personally abusive at times.
汤姆吗
Tom?
汤姆啊
Oh, Tom.
没想到他还有这倾向呢
I didn't know he had it in him.
他在那个部门就挺厉害的
He can be pretty able in that department.
可是先生 我现在想告诉您
But what I'm doing, sir, is I'm flagging to you
我非常渴望换个岗位
that I'm thirsty for the next chapter.
你帮我把这事办好再说
Well, you take care of this for me, and perhaps we'll talk.
懂吗 行了吗
OK? Done? Are we done?
灰常感谢
Muchly appreciated.
"灰常"
"Muchly"?
时候到了
Time's up.
国际与公共事务学院
是时候让那些媒体巨头停止毒害...
Time's up for the big media operations that poison...
国际与公共事务学院
-你看过这个吗  -泛美网络的节目
- Have you seen this? - ATN spot.
看来必须去 对吗
I guess we do, right?
你就站在那吗
You're gonna stand there?
离我一息之遥
In my air space?
我在重读
I'm re-reading it.
-这个内容  -抄送给你了
- For context. - You're CCed.
...一个人拥有的权力
...the power that one man wields.
我们不能仅仅因为太过恐惧一个人
We can't let these monopolistic practices go unchecked
拥有的权力 就放任那些
simply because we're too afraid
垄断情况不受限制地持续
of the power that one man wields.
韦斯达·罗伊科是美国核心的病灶
Waystar Royco is a cancer at the heart of America.
不敢相信 我居然靠骂我老爸来赚钱
I can't believe I'm getting paid to call my dad names.
太放纵了
It's so cathartic.
洛根·罗伊已经失控了...
Logan Roy is out of control...
你真希望他上泛美的节目吗
You really think he should do ATN?
是啊 当然 深入敌窝
Yeah. Sure. Into the lion's den.
他会攻击他们
He'll attack them,
正直的 旧约 反资本主义的吉尔
righteous, Old Testament, anti-capitalist Gil,
然后他们会攻击我们 "床上有共匪"
and they'll attack us, "There's a Red in the bed,"
他们得到观众 我们把基地炸了
they get the viewers and we get the base fired up.
没人会改变主意
No one's mind's getting changed,
然后一旦我们过了初步阶段
then once we're through the primaries,
-就转向中心  -除非吉尔不会转
- we pivot to center. - Except Gil won't pivot.
-我说不  -我会让他转的
- I say no! - I'll get him to pivot.
我说 再也不要了
I say no more!
-喂  -小西 是我
- Hello? - Hey, Shiv, it's me!
-汤姆 亲爱的  -听着
- Tom, sweetheart. - So listen,
有件事出了问题
something's afoot,
因为我们到了
because we've arrived at the drop-off point
我单身派对的下车点
for my bachelor party.
似乎计划有变
Seems there's been a change of plan,
我非常确定自己被整了
and I'm pretty sure I'm being pranked.
什么情况啊 罗曼
What's happening, Roman?
别问了小傻逼
Hold your tingling wiener.
待会儿就知道了
All will be clear soon.
我觉得你好像不懂在最后关头
I don't think you understand how disruptive it is
改旅行日程有多麻烦
to be changing the itinerary at this late stage.
我不知道会发生什么
I don't know what's gonna happen,
可我感觉肯定会有点恶心
but I've got a feeling it's liable to get a little disgusting.
我觉得你用不着跟我说这些
I don't think you're supposed to be telling me this.
我知道 只是
I know, I just
想跟你说一下 你懂的
wanted to flag it, and, you know,
不想良心不安 因为我 其实 从没...
calm the qualms, because I, for one, would never...
汤姆 就一晚上而已
Tom, it's one night,
大家都是成年人了
we're both adults,
尽情玩吧 好吗
just enjoy yourself, OK?
小西 亲爱的
Shiv, honey badger.
天呐 我真想和你共度良宵
God, I want to dock myself inside you
立刻马上
so much right now.
是吧 好了 我也爱你 汤姆
Yeah. OK. I love you too, Tom.
好的
Ok.
他终于肯赏脸加入我们了
Now he deigns to join us.
-你迟到了  -是啊 抱歉
- You're late. - Yeah, sorry.
我最近忙着改革技术融资
I've been a little busy revolutionizing tech financing.
购毒品吗
On coke.
希望不是 怎么样
Hope not. What up?
那么 谁想去日个流浪汉呢
So, who wants to fuck a hobo?
没人 好吧
No? All right,
那我们去聚会吧 就在那儿
then let's party. Down there.
什么... 别吧...
What... No...
我们要去隧道里办的派对吗
We're going to a party in the tunnel?
好吧 别这样 放轻松 我们不会
OK. No, relax, we're not going
去隧道里办的派对
to a party in a tunnel.
这只不过是他的诡计
This is just a ruse.
这是啥 那种会突然弹出来的玩意儿吗
What is this, some pop-up shit?
我需要穿上我的中欧大衣吗
Am I gonna need my central Europe coat?
小罗 我可穿着飞行袜和潮牌拖鞋呢
Romey, I'm wearing flight socks and my TSA slippers.
我知道你在耍什么把戏 好吗
I know what you're doing right now, OK?
我先被你骗进隧道
I'm being lured into a tunnel
接下来我就会在比利时醒来
and then next thing, I'm gonna wake up in Belgium
还他妈被刮了眉毛
with no frickin' eyebrows!
你应该会想把你的行李放到车里
You probably want to dump your luggage in the car.
我操
Shit.
伙计们
fellas.
抱歉 我们人已经够多了
Sorry, it's actually a really tight guest list.
罗曼
Roman.
-怎么了  -这可是马特和乔纳斯
- Yeah. - It's Matt and Jonas.
如果"苍蝇伙计"没在... 他们坐飞机来的
If the Fly Guys aren't on the... They flew in!
-罗曼  -放轻松 好吗
- Roman. - Relax, OK?
我们会搞定的 只是我们先进去
We're gonna figure it out. We're gonna first-wave it,
一到里面就给你们打电话 好吗
we'll call you once we're inside, all right?
要不这样 我请你们喝咖啡吧
You know what? Go get some coffees on me.
谢谢 不用了 我自己会买的
Thanks, we're good. I can buy coffee.
好吧 我们走吧
All right, let's go!
天呐
God!
我...
I...
我不能丢下"苍蝇伙计"
I can't just leave the Fly Guys.
这是"苍蝇伙计"的准则
That's the Fly Guy code.
好吧 把手机开着
OK, just leave your phones on,
-我会给你们打电话的  -好吧
- and I'll call ya. - All right.
-五分钟  -开着的
- Five minutes! - It's on.
好家伙
Man!
罗曼 你他妈到底给我准备了什么 兄弟
Roman. What the fuck have you got planned for me, man?
我认真的
No, seriously,
你到底准备了什么
what have you got planned?
汤姆 布拉格去不成了
Tom, Prague fell through,
我他妈又忙得不行
and I was fuckin' busy,
所以我没时间计划
and I didn't have time to plan
去摩纳哥的热气球
the hot air balloon to Monaco.
好吧 热气球
OK. Hot air balloon?
-是啊  -那应该很有趣的
- Yeah. - That would have been nice.
老哥 我的天哪 有只死老鼠
Dude! Oh, my God, that's a dead rat.
兄弟们 这里对鞋子真的很不友好
You guys, this is a disaster on the footwear front.
我能换双鞋吗
Can I change?
就是只死老鼠 谁会在乎啊
It's a dead rat. Who gives a shit?
当然 好吧 谢谢你 你们先走吧
Yeah, fine, thank you, just keep goin'.
-我们就来  -好吧 到那儿见
- We'll be here. - All right, see you over there.
你还受得了吗 要应付那么多酒精
Are you gonna be OK around all the booze
和白粉啥的玩意儿
and the coke and shit?
因为我敢肯定没人帮着你做这些
'Cause I can just make sure no one does it around you.
-我没事的  -真的吗
- I'll be fine. - Yeah?
-谢谢 老弟  -没事
- Thanks, bro. - Yeah. Of course.
等一下
Wait up!
老天爷啊 不就是只死老鼠吗 放轻松呗
Jesus fuckin' Christ, it's a dead rat. Relax.
听说你在开发软件
I hear you're doin' apps.
没错
Yeah.
还在孵化
I'm incubating.
我正在实现由编码到经济的转型
I'm rebalancing away from crypto into eco.
听起来... 未来感十足
Sounds... futuristico.
当然 那很好
Yeah, it's good.
总比整天被老爸揣在兜里好
It's better than being carried around in Dad's pockets
他妈的和精灵鼠小弟一样
like fuckin' Stuart Little.
兜里好处不少
They're nice pockets.
非常多
Spacious.
他怎么样了
How is he?
他嘛... 你知道的
He's... I mean, you know.
其实 他... 他让我监督
Actually, he's... he's got me overseeing
从种子岛发射的卫星
the satellite launch out of Tanegashima.
宇宙飞船
Spaceship?
可不是嘛 我还负责当地的交易
Yeah. Plus I'm heading up the local deal.
鲍勃·盖尔平在做销售
Bob Galpin is selling
我把他从公园部门赶出去了
and, I knocked it out of the park,
很不错
which is nice.
为你高兴 老弟
Good for you, bro.
是啊 看来我最终还是逃脱了牢笼吧
Yeah. Guess I finally broke out of the cage.
好狗是打不倒的 对吧 肯
Can't keep a good dog down, right, Ken?
汝等踏入此地之人 舍弃希望吧
Abandon all hope ye who enter.
-这是真的吗  -这真的是个走廊
- Is this real? - Is this a real corridor?
我们是要去飞机场吗
Are we goin' to an airfield?
格雷格 我告诉过你威拉
Greg, did I tell you that Willa
-搬去奥斯特里茨了吗  -是吗
- moved out to Austerlitz? - Oh?
是的 她喜欢那儿的静谧
Yeah, she loves how quiet it is.
她本来没想过自己会去 但她去了
She didn't think she would, but she does.
所以我肯定是不会纵情酒色了
So I for one won't be engaging in any debauchery.
罗曼·罗伊和他的客人们
Roman Roy and guests?
没错
That is correct.
-欢迎来到菱形派对  -谢谢
- Welcome to Rhomboid. - Thank you.
伙计们 把手机放进袋子里
Boys, we're pouching our phones.
等下 这就是了吗
Wait! Is this it?
这就是我的单身派对举办的地方吗
Is this actually where I'm going to have my bachelor party?
怎么这么潮湿 我觉得这儿肯定有个大裂缝
Why is it so wet? I think there's a big leak somewhere.
我已经为了缓解时差
I've been living on central European time
适应中欧时间两天了
for 48 hours to ease the transition.
我不久就要准备吃早餐了
I'm gonna be ready for breakfast soon.
我不确定这个派对上会不会有很多吃的
I don't know if this is the kind of party with a lot of food.
罗曼 不好意思 咱们要在这搞我的单身派对吗
Roman, I'm sorry, is this where I'm having my bachelor party?
罗曼 怎么样 兄弟
Roman, how are you, man?
肯 好久不见
Ken. Long time.
我们还好吧
Are we good?
你是我第三久的朋友
You're my third-oldest friend.
你他妈把我耍得团团转
You fucked me like a tied goat.
-我们可"好"了  -没错
- We're great. - No, yeah,
你们走对了 继续直走
you're goin' the right way. Keep goin' straight.
-肯德尔 我想说  -怎么了
- Kendall, I was gonna say. - Yeah?
如果你今晚需要什么
If you need anything tonight,
一瓶水 软饮料
bottle of water, soft drink,
尽管吩咐 我就是你的骡子
whatever, I'm gonna be your mule.
其实吧 我需要点菜单上没有的
Actually, you know what? I need something a little off-menu.
看看你能不能帮我搞点克他命[致幻麻醉剂]
See if you can find me some ketamine.
我不知道那是什么
I don't know what that is.
桑迪在吗 我们多久谈事
Is Sandy here? When do we sit?
别担心 一切准备就绪
Yeah, yeah, all things in time.
这边
Right here.
抱歉
Sorry.
这一定会很精彩的 谢了 罗曼
Well. Now I'm sure it's gonna be great. Thanks, Roman.
你在期望什么 你当初怎么想到请我帮忙 汤姆
What did you expect? Why'd you even ask me, Tom?
我以为你会应付自如呢
Thought you'd rise to the occasion.
是啊 很明显我没有
Well, clearly I haven't risen to the occasion.
男士们 祝你们有个无与伦比的夜晚
Gents, have a great fuckin' night.
德米特里 你还好吗
Dmitri, how are you?
肯德尔 我待会来找你 好吗
Kendall. I'll find you, all right?
好了 就是这儿了
OK. This is it.
怎么样 牛不牛逼
Yeah? Cool, right?
牛逼吗 还是说 全是他妈的扯淡
Is it cool, or is it, like, total fucking bullshit?
这什么呀 这什么呀
Well, what is it? What is it?
这就是肉体狂欢圣殿
It's a physical fun palace.
就是说 只要你想要 女人也会想要
It's basically, if you're into it, and she's into it,
都挺好的
it's all good.
快看这个戴鸟面具的家伙
Look at this fucking guy with the bird mask
像"大开眼戒"似的[美国惊悚剧情片]
like Eyes Wide Shut.
厉害 "大开..."
Oh, wow. Eyes w...
等等 这会变成狂欢吗
Wait, is this... is this gonna be an orgy?
-不会  -这不会变成狂欢
-No. - This is not gonna be an orgy?
格雷格 又不是97年 它不是这样 也不是那样
Greg, it's not 1997. It's not this, it's not that.
不要二元地看东西 老古董[盒式录像机]
Don't be so binary, Mr. Betamax.
那会不会有一点点像狂欢呢
Is it gonna be like a little bit of an orgy?
基本上就是一群帅哥美女...
It's basically a collective of hot people...
跟康纳... 在派对上
and Connor... at a party.
显然还有一只打扮成宇航员的猴子
And a monkey dressed as an astronaut, apparently.
你想什么 它就是什么
It's whatever you want it to be.
它是为突现行为搞的沙坑
It's a fucking sand pit for emergent behavior.
行了 老天啊 太... 好
OK, OK, holy shit. So... OK. OK.
是不是说 我们可以... 在这做爱
So, does that mean we're able to... fuck here?
是的 肯 你觉得那只"小猫咪"怎么样 上吗
Yeah. Hey, Ken, what do you think of the pussycat? On it?
不 跟我无关 做生意就是做爱
No, not me. Business is my fucking.
很好 我给你找个彭博终端 好让你把老二插进去
Great. I'll find you a Bloomberg terminal to stick your dick in.
彭博终端: 查阅和分析实时金融市场数据的计算机系统
我退出 我在谈恋爱 有对象的
Well, I'm out. In a relationship. Girlfriend!
不得不说 罗曼 看起来希望很大
I gotta say, Roman, this is looking promising.
狂欢的希望非常大
This is looking really promising!
是吧 对我有点信心
See? Have a little faith.
这里有那种区域 对吗
There's areas, though, right?
就是那种中立区域
Neutral areas in terms of not being, you know,
不强制搞色情的事
compulsory to do sex stuff?
不行 格雷格 如果你拒绝 他们会切掉你的丁丁
No, Greg. If you refuse, they cut your dick off.
我刚才怎么说的 这是你情我愿的事
What did I just say? It's very consensual.
安吉拉
Angela.
Angela?
安吉拉 安吉拉
Angela. Angela.
达斯特
Yo. Dust.
-我操  -怎么了
- Oh. Fuck. - Hey. What's up?
发生什么事了
Yeah, hey, what's happening?
我们现在在这个破仓库
Here we are in a fuckin' warehouse
-在日落公园还是什么鬼  -对
- in Sunset Park or whatever. - Yeah.
我感觉这就是共时性原则
I feel like this is synchronicity.
共时性: "说曹操曹操到"等神秘现象 也可称"巧合"
不是吗 就像宇宙在启示我们一些事
Yeah? Like the universe is telling us something.
是的 很感谢你来见我们
Yeah. We really appreciated you coming to see us.
没事 没事
Yeah, yeah, totally,
我超级兴奋
I'm super-excited.
当然了 我也是
Yeah. Totally. Me too.
那好 行吧 好极了 就这样
OK, well, fuck, yeah. Excellent. All right.
就这样 很高兴见到你
All right. Good to see you.
好
Yeah.
我在想
You know, I was thinking,
要不你喝一杯酒 再喝一杯水
maybe one wine, one water,
就像团队潜规则那样的
as like an informal rule for the group?
他们还有意大利调味饭球
Also, uh, they have risotto balls.
就像酒量很大 海量的人
Like, they're soakers. Super-soakers.
-克他命  -格雷格 格雷格
- Ketamine. - Greg! Greg!
给你搞到一个 来啊兄弟 今晚嗨爆
Got you one. Come on, man, it's goin' off tonight!
我们该找个姑娘聊聊
We should talk to some girls.
给你个小建议 问她们911时在哪里
A little tip. Ask 'em where they were on 9/11.
如果不知道 说明她们还不到21岁
If they don't know, they could be under 21.
小西给了我嘿咻通行证
Well, Shiv gave me a hall pass.
因为显然我们是成年人了
'Cause we're adults. Apparently.
我要多发射点存货[精液]
I'm gonna blow my load like multiple times.
那... 小西也有同样的安排吗
Wow. So... And Shiv has that same arrangement?
她也是个成年人嘛...
She's an adult too, so...
什么 不是的
What? No, no.
是的 确定
Well, yeah, sure.
我不知道 格雷格 这又不是比赛
I mean, I don't know, Greg. It's not a competition.
当然 当然不是 没事
No, no, no. That's cool.
我相信你们都理清楚了吧
I'm sure you guys have it all figured out.
-小罗 这是什么  -摇头丸 快乐丸
- Romey, what is this? - Molly. Happy pills.
-很酷  -但我不...
- Oh, cool. - But I wouldn't...
不 不 不 按布拉格时间
No, no, no, no. Prague time.
现在是凌晨两点 我需要点提神的东西
It's two in the morning for me. I need a little pick-me-up.
-别  -伙计 我了解自己
- Don't. - Dude. I know my way around.
1986年 我 一张弗利特伍德麦克唱片
1986, me, a Fleetwood Mac LP,
还有一袋大麻 我们触碰到了上帝面颊
and a bag of weed touched the face of God.
今晚第一次 以后还会有很多次
Huh? The first of the evening, the first of many.
-别再多嗑这个了  -好的 一粒就够了
- Do not do any more of these. - Got it. I'm one and done.
筹备着很多新鲜玩意
Got a lot of shit cookin',
比如 人造太阳能电话...
like, artificial sun solar cells thing...
好的 听着 伙计 投票那事
Yeah. Listen, man, about the vote,
你爸 跟咱俩
and your dad and us,
我爱你 但你知道我追逐的是钱
I love you, man, but you know I had to follow the money.
你知道的吧
You know that, right?
我理解
I get it.
好的 咱们为什么不私下聊会呢
All right. Hey, why don't we talk in private for a second?
-我们可以吗  -就在这儿聊
- Can we do that? - We can talk right here.
好的
All right.
那听好 我有个问题问你
So listen, I have a question for you.
你全身而退怎么样
How would you like to be all the way out?
五个亿 买你在韦斯达的股份
Half a bill for your share of Waystar.
-真的吗  -当然 伙计
- Is this for real? - Yeah, man.
我他妈感觉自己很慷慨 就这么回事
I'm feelin' fuckin' generous, that's all.
我就想睡个好觉[丰盈枕头] 所以额外加了好处
And I've plumped the pillows and added a little premium.
-包括什么  -全是流动资金
- Consisting of what? - Straight liquid.
-放屁  -这点你不用担心
- Bullshit. - Don't you worry about it.
我可以加
I can raise it.
为什么你还想买更多
Why would you want to be even more in?
那地方就他妈是家古董店
The place is a fuckin' antique shop.
肯 请你拿着钱退出吧 求你了
Ken, just take the money and get out. Please.
我是说...
I mean...
我不算没有兴趣
it's not uninteresting.
好 好极了 听好了
Fantastic. Great. So listen,
这事分两步
there's a part two to this.
为什么不和桑迪聊聊这个事
Why don't we talk this over with Sandy?
桑迪... 弗尼斯吗
Sandy... Furness?
跟我来
Come with me.
过来
Come.
干杯
Bottom's up.
-一 二 三  -克他命
- One, two, three! - Ketamine.
-你还好吗  -请摆上一排
- You good? - Line 'em up, please.
这些浴袍不错
These bathrobes are nice.
看见了吗
See these?
你的桌布哲学是什么
What's your table linen philosophy?
我的哲学是我真的不在乎
Uh, my philosophy is I literally don't give a fuck.
那是什么 尼采吗
So what's that, Nietzsche?
这些是我们注册表上的
These are what's on our registry.
你应该选这些
You should go for these.
好的 你想要咱们使用匹配餐具吗
Right, you want us to have matching cutlery?
为什么不呢
Why not?
会很糟糕 也很可爱
It'll be sort of horrible, and cute.
那等我们都离婚了 分完家产后
So when we both get divorced and split all our stuff,
还可以联系一下 搞同样的餐具
we can hook up and have the same set.
全套
The full set.
是的
Yeah.
你知道这不过是找乐子 对吧
You know this is just fun, right?
-我知道 但就是...  -没事的
- I know, it's just... - It's nothing.
它不是什么东西 又没有上帝
I mean, it's not anything. There's no God,
也没有... 任何东西
there's no... anything,
只不过是人们在房间里
there's just people in rooms
试图找点乐子而已
trying to be happy.
-对吗  -对
- Right? - Right.
对了 我跟吉尔建议
Oh, and I suggested to Gil
让他今晚在泛美节目里少提点反韦斯达的议题
that he cool off on the anti-Waystar agenda on ATN tonight.
-你说什么  -对
- Excuse me? - Yeah.
我跟他提过这事了
I talked to him at the thing.
好吧
Oh. OK.
虽然我的确花了点时间
Well, I did spend quite some time
研究如何十分生动地在韦斯达的电视网上
on how it'd be very vivid to attack Waystar
-攻击韦斯达 但是...  -十分生动
- on a Waystar network, but... - Very vivid?
那已经没用了 让我们看起来像有议题一样
It's played out. Makes it look like we have an agenda.
我们确实有啊
Uh, we do.
别让过于强大的媒体拥有者们
Stopping overly mighty media owners
为我们的民主制定议程
setting the agenda for our democracy.
司法部 联邦通信委员会 蝙蝠侠
DOJ, FCC, Batman,
阻止你老爸吞噬这些新闻
to stop your dad eating the news.
好吧 但即使我们做到那一步
OK, but even if we're going for that,
难道不会变成什么没人拜读的宏大演讲吗
isn't that in some big speech that no one reads?
难道他今晚就不能想想美国 忘掉基地吗
Can't he just connect to America tonight and forget the base?
小西 我理解你希望两头都不得罪的想法
Shiv, I appreciate you might have split loyalties on this.
扯淡 我在努力让他赢
Fuck you. I'm just trying to make him win.
我觉得他没法同时兼顾
I don't think he can do both at once.
我觉得吉尔兼顾不了基地和其他
I don't think Gil can do the base and the rest.
没那个金刚钻
Well, if he can't ride two horses at once,
他就不该揽那瓷器活
he shouldn't be working at the circus.
-桑迪也会来这种地方吗  -对啊 他喜欢嘿嘿嘿
- Sandy comes to these? - Oh, yeah. He loves sex.
伙计 他把用来尿尿的东西
Dude, the thing that he pees through,
放到别人身体里
he puts into other people.
真他妈恶心 而且对象还不少
It's fucking vile. And a lot.
好哇 桑迪
Hey, Sandy.
先生们 失陪
Oh. Gents, excuse me.
-肯德尔 你状态不错  -谢谢
- Kendall. You look well. - Thank you.
你看上去 有点格格不入
You look, uh, out of place.
我就喜欢看年轻人嬉戏打闹
I do like to see the youngsters frolic.
想聊聊吗
So, you wanna talk?
斯图伊跟你详细说了吗
Uh, did Stewy fill you in?
我怎么感觉 我就要发现
Why do I feel like I'm about to find out
你们并不是我的衣食父母了
you're not my real mommy and daddy after all?
事实是
Look, the truth is,
他想吃掉你的那杯羹
he wants your piece of pie,
可是... 求别在这发脾气 成吗
but... and please don't fucking blow a fuse here, OK?
事实是 他半边身子已经进韦斯达了
The reality is, he's already in on Waystar.
-此话怎讲  -桑迪就是我
- As in? - As in Sandy's me,
我代表桑迪
and I'm Sandy.
我们就像单一的实体
We're like a single entity.
像从神话里跳出来的生物
Like a creature from mythology.
长着骏马头和天鹅屌的那种
You know, head of a horse, dick of a swan.
斯图伊... 说真的吗
Stewy... seriously?
我的一家空壳公司连着他的私募股权基金
I have a shell company attached to his private equity fund.
我是寄生虫身上的寄生虫
I'm a parasite on a parasite.
我拉你入伙的时候 你就该把事情跟我讲明
You should have disclosed that to me when I brought you in.
你说得完全正确
You are one hundred percent
我早就该告诉你的
correct about that. I should have done that.
你现在处境艰难
You were in a tough position
完全不用考虑
without having to consider whether your dad
你爸是否想让我参与
would want me involved.
他肯定不想的
He very much would not.
显而易见 我女友的焦虑症发作了
So apparently, my girlfriend's having a panic attack.
我就先让你俩好好聊聊 行吧
I'm gonna let you two just catch up now. Cool?
斯图伊跟我说 你要进军科技领域
Stewy tells me you're getting into tech.
对 我有个基金
Yeah, I have a fund.
我们找到了商机 但已经搭桥了
We're niche, but we're engaged.
其实今晚刚谈成一笔
Just closed a deal tonight, actually.
我找到这四个斯坦福的毕业生
And I found these four Stanford grads
准备要做这个 相当酷了
who are doing this thing, it's pretty cool,
他们发明了一种氢灯...
they have this cluster of hydrogen lamps...
等等 什么情况
Wait. What's going on?
伙计 你在搞推销吗 你在推销吗
Dude, are you pitching? You just pitch?
你打哪冒出来的 海地吗
Where'd you spring from, Heidi?
别停啊 我想听你们讲卖点 没准我会投资
Don't stop. I want to hear the pitch. I might invest.
我们只是聊聊
We were just talking.
跟他聊 敌人吗
To him? The enemy?
大人说话小孩别插嘴 你去其他房间玩怎么样
The adults are talking. How about you go play in the other room?
那啥 桑迪 我能私下跟你谈谈吗
Hey, Sandy, could I maybe get a moment with you in private?
我想跟你谈谈 你对你那五十家失败的
I'd like to talk to you about how attached you're feeling
本地电视台有什么感觉
to your 50 failing local TV stations.
当然 我们肯定能找到合适的时间
Sure. I'm sure we could find a time.
罗曼 你能稍微离开二十分钟吗
Roman, could you maybe back off for, like, 20 minutes?
-不干  -去给我们拿杯喝的
- No. - Yeah. Get us a drink?
我很乐意再来一杯古典鸡尾酒
I would love another old-fashioned.
他很乐意再来一杯古典鸡尾酒 可真陈腐
He would love another old-fashioned, cliché that he is.
不可能 鬼才给你拿
No, that's not gonna happen.
我知道你跟我爸
I know that you and my dad
恨不得一口把对方活吃了
have been deeply and madly in hate with each other,
而且你们积怨已深
and you have been for many years,
但我想让你知道 我做得了主
but I want you to know that I'm my own thing,
我完全有权...
and I am fully authorized...
我完全有权
I am fully authorized
来代表罗根进行谈判
to negotiate on behalf of Logan.
他在当狗腿子 就像1985年那会儿
Yeah, he's doing satellites like it's 1985.
老爸让他在后座抓住塑料方向盘
Dad's got him holding the plastic steering wheel in the back
再告诉他是他在驾驶
and telling him he's driving.
你得原谅我哥
You have to excuse my brother.
他的药劲还没缓过来呢
He's adjusting to his medication right now.
你滚回去跟你那群狐朋狗友玩不好吗
How about you fuck off back to your little gang-bang?
-听到他怎么呵斥我了吧  -你在丢自己的脸
- See how he talks to me? - You're embarrassing yourself.
-你们可是一家人  -他以前经常把我锁在笼子里
- You're family. - He used to lock me in a cage.
-什么鬼  -可不 这是真的
- What the fuck? - No, that's a true story.
干嘛 你要装作不记得狗笼那回事了吗
What, you're pretending that you don't remember the dog pound?
-你嗑嗨了吗  -那是个"游戏"
- Are you tripping? - Yeah, it was a "Game."
我得爬到厨房里巨大的狗笼子里
I had to go climb in this big dog cage in the kitchen
等着有人来找我
and wait for someone to come collect me.
是吗 我反正是不知道
Oh, yeah? Well, I-I don't know.
可能要等三分钟 也可能是一个下午
Might be three minutes, might be the whole afternoon.
我才四岁 就吃一个冰冷的锡碗里的狗粮
Four years old. I was eating dog food out of a cold tin bowl.
很残忍 对吧
I know, right? They should
他们该找人来拍个电影的 对吧
make a fuckin' movie of this shit, right?
恕我失陪
Excuse me.
我会回来的
I'll be back.
-你他妈在搞毛啊  -什么
- What the fuck are you doing? - What?
-满嘴喷的什么鬼  -我想说什么就说什么
- What was that bullshit? - I can say what I want.
但是你... 太疯癫了 你简直跟疯了一样
Yeah, but you... That was insane. You're acting insane.
那你要我装作什么都没发生过吗
So you just want me to pretend that none of that happened?
发生了什么
What happened?
什么都没发生过 狗笼那事根本不存在
None of it happened. Dog pound didn't happen.
我从没逼你吃过狗粮
I never made you eat dog food.
有个碗里盛满了吃的
There was a bowl that was filled with chow,
我必须吃干净了才能从笼子里出来
and I couldn't leave the cage until I finished it.
那就是个游戏 你乐在其中
It was a game, you enjoyed it.
去问康纳 去问小西
A-Ask Connor. Ask Shiv.
我居然喜欢被绳子拴着待在笼子里吗
I enjoyed being in a cage with a leash around my neck?
绳子又是从哪冒出来的 你尽胡说八道
So now there's a leash? You're full of shit.
我 我胡说八道
Me? I'm full of shit?
-玩得开心  -快他妈滚
- Have fun. - Get the fuck outta here.
混蛋 操
Asshole! Nwahh!
-我得到了匹阉马吗  -栗褐色
- So I got this gelding, right? - Chestnut brown.
你不会相信那货的脑袋有多大
You wouldn't believe the size of this guy's cranium.
可大了
Big ol' noggin!
老康 我能问你点事吗
Hey! Con, can I ask you something?
你还记得
Do you remember anything
我们小时候有过狗笼这回事吗
about a dog pound when we were growing up?
当然 这是你以前经常玩的游戏
Sure, I remember that game you used to play.
他真的把我锁在破狗笼里过对吧
So he used to lock me in a fucking cage.
对啊 大笼子 在你妈家里
Sure, the big cage, yeah, in your mother's place.
在切尔滕纳姆的洗衣房里
The laundry room in Cheltenham.
切尔滕纳姆: 英国英格兰西南部城市
谢了 他还想忽悠[煤气灯]我
Thank you! He's trying to gaslight me.
煤气灯效应: 洗脑和心理掌控 出自1944年惊悚电影"煤气灯下"
不 你挺喜欢玩的
No, you liked it!
你主动要求被锁到笼子里
You asked to be put in that cage.
-你说啥  -真的
- What? - Yeah.
我觉得很奇怪 但你确实乐在其中
It was really weird, but I think you enjoyed it.
好吧 我还主动要求吃狗粮了吗
OK, so I asked to eat dog food?
你吃的应该是巧克力蛋糕
It was chocolate cake. I think.
-胡说八道  -我不知道
- Bullshit. - I don't know.
不 肯德尔把我锁在笼子里 我性格就变得古怪
No. Kendall locked me in a cage, I went weird,
就开始尿床
I started wetting the bed,
所以老爸把我送去了圣安德鲁斯
and that's why Dad sent me away to St. Andrews.
不对 小罗 老爸送你去军事学校
No, Rome, Dad sent you to military school
因为是你主动要求的
because you asked to go.
-你他妈满嘴谎话  -我记得就是这样的
- Oh, you're full of shit! - That's how I remember it!
听我说 我的农场
So listen, my ranch
可以完美防御任何生化袭击
is completely safe from biological or chemical attack.
-这些是你的朋友对吧  -对
- These are your friends, right? - Yeah.
欢迎你们 随时到我的农场来 世界末日前后都行
You'd all be welcome, anytime, pre- or post-apocalypse.
汤姆
Tom!
-汤姆  -你好
- Tom. - Hey.
你看到肯德尔了吗
Have you seen Kendall?
没有
No.
我感觉咱们得时刻盯着他才行
I feel like we should maybe keep an eye out for him.
操
Aw, damn it.
汤姆 亲爱的 我正跟吉尔在泛美
Tom, sweetheart, I'm at ATN with Gil.
你尽量长话短说
What's the least amount of syllables you can say this in?
我就想弄清一件有关你我的事
Well, I just want to be clear in terms of you and me.
这是个有报酬的安排吗
Is this a quid pro quo arrangement?
不知道你在胡说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
就是 如果我...
It's just, you know, if I...
如果我 打个比方
if I, for instance,
我要是摸了奶
if I touch a boob,
你会抓人家屌吗
do you grab a dick?
我不知道这...
I don't know if that's a...
我就想大概讲清楚
Just to get a rough chart of comparison
对比华氏和摄氏
from Fahrenheit to Celsius,
以眼还眼
or, you know, an eye for an eye?
以穴还穴
Or an orifice for an orifice?
我就是想心里有点哔数
I'm just trying to get a sense of the parameters here.
汤姆 我现在不方便跟你谈
Uh, Tom, I can't negotiate right now.
我们懂的 对吧 都懂的
But we know, right? We just know.
当然
Sure.
我们懂的
We know.
你想梳理一遍怎么应对私人事务吗
So you want to run the tree on how personal stuff plays?
议题 议题 议题
Issues, issues, issues.
我能应付他们的奉承 小西
I can handle the soft soap, Shiv.
肯德尔 刚跟小西谈过
Hey, Kendall. Just spoke to Shiv.
她正式同意我们找乐子了
Official permission for having of the fun.
真好 为你开心
Amazing. So happy for you.
老兄 能帮我...
Hey, man, can I get this, uh...
-肯  -弗兰克 听着
- Hey, Ken. - Hey, Frank. Listen.
我刚接洽完
I've had an approach.
这次接洽挺有意思的
It's kind of a very interesting approach,
我想听听你的意见
and I wanted to get your brain on it.
那些姑娘们给我回信了 达斯特 玩艺术那家
I heard from the girls. The Dust thing. With the art?
对 我见过她们了 这事儿定了
Yeah, I know. I saw them. It's locked down.
她们想让你知道 之前跟你谈得很愉快 不过...
They wanted you to know they loved you in the room. But...
我才和姑娘们聊过 没问题
I just spoke to the girl. We're good.
肯 她们已经找别处张罗了
Ken, they're already setting this up elsewhere.
但我说过了
But like I said,
她们之前和你谈得很愉快
they loved you in the room.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
我猜她们更喜欢其他人的报价
I think there's other money and they liked it better.
那我们加价
Then we match it.
我试过了 可...
I tried that already, but...
讲真 她们和你谈得很愉快
Seriously, they loved you in the room.
你他妈能别重复她们和我谈得很愉快了吗
Will you stop telling me they loved me in the fucking room?!
弗兰克 我第一次就听见了
Frank! I heard you the first time.
行 行吧 我跟她谈谈
OK. OK, let me talk to her.
我能搞定
I can fix this.
我们能谈一会儿吗
Hey. Hey. Can we talk for a second?
下次再说行吗
Can we do this another time?
我刚和弗兰克打过电话
I just got off the phone to Frank.
怎么回事 他都跟我说了
What happened? He told me.
很抱歉 不是针对你
I'm sorry, it's nothing personal.
我不该跟你讲这些
I shouldn't be telling you this,
我打算投资一大笔种子基金
but I'm about to land a chunk of seed capital
像爱达荷州那么大的规模
the size of fuckin' Idaho,
无论你需要什么
so, I mean, whatever it is you need,
我都能帮你实现 懂吗
I can make it happen. OK?
-行吧  -可以吗
- Yeah, OK. - OK?
那我们说好了
So are we good?
其实和钱无关
You know, it's just not about that.
那是为什么 指点一下呗
Then, like, help me out here,
还是我没注意到什么
'cause there's something I'm not seeing.
-是名字  -哪个 是指达斯特吗
- It's the name. - Which? You mean "Dust"?
是罗伊 肯德尔·罗伊
Roy. Kendall Roy.
好像我嫁给了希特勒一样
It'd be like I was marrying Hitler,
那我不就变成希特勒夫人了
and then I'd get to be, what, Mrs. Hitler?
这么讲并不公平
OK, uh, that's not really fair,
那... 那不是我
Look, that's... that's not me.
我不是罗伊家的
I'm not a Roy.
好吗 不算是
OK? Not really.
抱歉 没事的 我们只是不想成为希特勒...
I'm sorry. It's cool, we just don't want to be Hitler Incorp...
能请你别说希特勒吗 你又不了解我
Can you stop saying Hitler? Please? You don't know what I am.
外面都说你是个吸毒的垃圾 连屎都拉不好
Consensus is you're a coked-up prick who can't shit straight.
你以为自己有所不同吗
You think you're different?
安吉拉 慢着
OK, Angela. You know what,
老实跟你说...
I'm gonna be frank with you...
我不想在这儿谈这事
Look, I didn't want to do this here.
没准是因为嗑了可卡因 所以我比较直接
And I may be being more forthright 'cause of the coke.
一般我嗑嗨了都会这样
I tend to get more forthright on coke.
懂吗 抱歉
All right? I'm sorry.
滚开
Hey, fuck off!
兄弟 我能来点吗
Hey, man, can I get in on this?
今天来到演播间的是吉尔·伊维斯参议员
I'm joined in the studio by Senator Gil Eavis. Firstly, Senator,
欢迎 感谢您参与本次节目
welcome. We really appreciate it.
很高兴来到这儿 莎伦
Happy to be here, Sharon.
那我就开门见山了
I want to just jump straight in, if we may.
十八个月前你的妻子不幸自杀
Your wife very tragically took her own life 18 months ago.
泛美最热烈的欢迎方式
The warmest of ATN welcomes.
相信所有人都知道那件事了
I think everybody knows about that,
我每天都很痛苦
and it's something I live with every day.
不过这和今天的议题无关
But it's not relevant to the issues.
-我想要探讨...  -但你给大家的印象是
- I want to explore... - The impression you've given
你是因此才竞选总统的
is that it did inform your decision to run.
很多事都会促发这类重大决定
A lot of things inform a big decision like this.
不过我今晚想说的是...
But what I want to talk about tonight...
但事情过去还没多久
But it hasn't been long,
我猜有些人会想问的是
and I guess that what some people may ask is,
是什么导致了这场悲剧的发生
what could possibly have caused such a tragedy?
你是否这么快就
And are you ready so suddenly
准备好转身投入到总统竞选
to turn around and run for the highest office?
他不是准备了这个问题吗
Doesn't he have a line for this?
这基本上... 没什么问题
It's usually... normally OK.
我现在关心的是 我认为这个国家需要
I'm focused on what I think this country needs to do
-去向...  -所以你已经考虑过了
- to move to... - So you have thought about it,
你的心理和情绪状况
your mental and emotional state?
我会考虑自己的情感 和多数人类一样...
I think about my feelings, like most humans...
不 不 不 别冷嘲热讽
Oh, no, no. No sarcasm.
像你现在这样忙于应付
It must be incredibly difficult for you
那些说你有心理问题的漫天谣言
as a person who has had to deal with rumors
一定非常不容易吧
swirling about the state of his mental health.
能不能别玩这套 假装同情
Why don't we stop playing this game of pretend sympathy
实际上缺是在诱导观众去问出
where you're just trying to get your viewers to ask,
"老公得是什么样子才会让老婆自杀"
"What sort of guy has a wife who kills herself?"
-那是...  -你想上升到个人层面吗
- That is... - You wanna make this personal?
我们来谈谈洛根·罗伊吧 行吗
Let's talk about Logan Roy, shall we?
那个今天安排你黑我的幕后黑手...
The paymaster who set you up in this hack job against me today...
参议员 不是吧
Oh, Senator, come on.
如果你想了解一个人
If you want to know about a person,
就去了解他的家庭关系
look at his relationships with his family.
他的独女
His only daughter
-在为我工作  -干你娘
- has come to work for me. - Oh, fuck off.
-小西  -怎么就拿我说起事了
- Shiv. - I'm not the fucking angle.
所以你不打算继续回答问题了吗
So you don't want to take any more questions?
肯定不再回答你了 谢谢
Certainly not from you. Thank you.
真是抱歉 看来
Unfortunately, that seems to be
以上就是我们和吉尔·伊维斯参议员的全部访谈
all the time we're going to have with Senator Eavis.
小肯
Hey! Kenny!
你抽得有点凶啊 老哥
Whoa. That's a chunk of chang you got there, buddy.
没错 格雷格
It sure is, Greg.
能不能... 悠着... 悠着点 好吗
Maybe... just ease... ease into that, right?
别一下全抽了
I mean, not all at once?
你找我有事吗 兄弟
Can I help you with something, man?
你他妈在搞毛 一整天都跟在我屁股后面
What the fuck's going on? You've been up my ass all night.
没啊 我就... 我就是看着你点
No, I just... I'm just keepin' an eye out for you.
毒品这种... 你不知道哪里就...
I mean, drugs... You don't know where...
是拉瓦吗 她让你这么干的吗
Is this Rava? Did she put you up to this?
不是
No.
那你他妈在搞啥啊
Then what's your fuckin' deal, man?
你的父亲有点担心你罢了
Your dad is, I think, a little worried about you is all.
我爸让你他妈来监视我
My dad asked you to fuckin' spy on me?
不是监视 是照看...
No, not spy, watch...
家人般地照看你
Family-style watching you.
我刚抽了四条可卡因
I'm about to do these four lines of cocaine,
马上还要再抽四条
to top up the four I just did,
然后我的心脏就会爆炸
and then my heart's gonna explode.
你要是想阻止我
So if you want to stop me,
随你便
be my guest.
我不抽白粉
I don't do white drugs.
要是他儿子吸毒过量
My dad's gonna be super-disappointed
我爸肯定会很失望
if his son ODs.
-我知道  -所以...
- I know. - So...
什么鬼
What the fuck?
他指望着你照顾我呢
He's counting on you to look after me.
行 行 行 停下 停下
OK, OK, OK! Stop. Stop.
好吧 给我
OK. Give it to me.
-上啊  -我会上的
- Go on. - I'm goin'.
格雷格
Greg!
上吧 格雷格
Go for it, Greg!
吸掉那几条粗壮的可卡因吧 你这死变态
Suck on those big white dicks, you fuckin' pervert.
格雷格 你这杂种可真贪心
Greg, you greedy piece of shit.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
格雷格 你简直是可卡因狂魔啊
Greg, you total coke whore.
我应该吐吗
Should I puke?
除非你能把你全身的血吐干净
Not unless you can puke up your entire bloodstream.
-我的天 伙计  -这药好猛啊
- Oh, my God, man. - That is strong drugs.
-我知道 但愿你不会死  -我的天呐
- I know. I hope you don't die. - Oh, my God!
如果你死了 心脏会跳动得非常猛烈
If you do, your heart is gonna be pumping so hard
没准还能让你死而复生
it'll probably bring you back to life.
-他去哪了  -系好安全带吧 你这蠢货
- Where did he go? - Buckle up, fucklehead!
好哇
Hi.
-晚上好 小美女  -晚上好
- Hello, Pinky. - Hello.
-很高兴你来赴约了  -家人嘛
- I'm glad you kept the date. - Well, family.
-话剧怎么样  -你知道的
- How was the play? - Oh, you know,
人们假扮他人
people pretending to be people.
婚礼安排得怎么样了
How are the wedding arrangements?
非常激动人心
Very exciting.
是吧 我也很激动 乖女儿
Yeah, well, I'm excited. My daughter.
所以你看过采访了
So you saw the interview.
他们告诉我了
They told me.
你攻陷那男人的妻子
You came after the man's wife.
他们是这么说的
They said.
你对这没意见吗
You're OK with that?
告诉他不要谈论我的家族
Tell him not to speak about my family,
不要在我的电视网上...
not on my network...
以及其他任何电视网上 再也不要
not on any network, ever again.
不然我就摧毁他
Or I'll end him.
可不是 让那位说你在压制异议的人闭嘴
Yeah, silence the man who says you're stifling dissent.
他怎么敢说我不是好父亲
I'm a bad father? How dare he.
他还他妈不是好丈夫呢 他杀了自个儿老婆
He's a bad fuckin' husband. He killed his wife.
算了吧 爸
Oh, come on. Dad.
如果你正在进行的收购
What if the acquisitions you're making
真的对国家不利呢
are actually bad for the country?
他在利用你 你难道不明白吗
He's using you. Can't you see it?
别让任何那些屁话扫了你婚礼的兴
Don't let any of the bullshit overshadow your wedding.
婚礼
The wedding?
还管什么破婚礼 我他妈一点不在乎
The fucking wedding? I don't give a shit.
西沃恩 别这样 别再胡闹了
Siobhan, come on. Stop screwing around.
我想好好谈谈你的事
I want to talk about you properly.
回来吧 我厌倦应付这些了
Come in. I'm tired of this.
你有潜力
You have potential.
我一直觉得你是最聪明的
I've always thought you were the smartest.
所以你就先给了肯德尔和罗曼机会吗
So that's why you tried Kendall and Roman first?
其实吧 我确实是最聪明的
You know what? I am the smartest.
所以我可以看穿你
Which is why I can see through you
以及你虚情假意来收买我的小提议
and this transparent little offer to buy me off.
我一直努力公平地对待你 西沃恩
I've always tried to do right by you, Siobhan.
但也许...
And maybe...
也许我本该不用
maybe I shouldn't have.
也许我就该让他们冲着你来
Maybe I should just let them come for you.
比如谁
Like who?
比如... 我不知道
Like... I don't know.
但我听说了一些事
But I hear things.
你是在威胁我吗
Are you threatening me?
绝对不是
Absolutely not.
如果事情要这样发展的话 那滚吧 爸
If this is the way things are gonna go, then fuck off, Dad.
那... 我就对不住了
Then... I'm truly sorry.
关于小西
So, in terms of Shiv,
我争取到可以做的是
where I've landed is
也许就找个人帮我打飞机
I'm maybe just gonna ask for a handy.
-你觉得可以吗  -别提前找借口
- Think that's OK? - Don't pre-rationalize.
你享乐 把羞耻心当甜点吞下去
You get off, you eat the shame for dessert.
-慢着 她吗 那个女人  -是啊 我们聊了
- Wait. Her? That one? - Yeah. We were talking
大概二十分钟的金融衍生品
for, like, 20 minutes about financial derivatives,
然后她就邀请我了
and she just asked me.
我的天 真他妈要命
My God! Holy shit!
老爹我他妈会为她发狂 你应该去啊
Dad would go fuckin' nuts for her. You should do it.
-是吗  -是啊 当然了
- Yeah? - Yeah! Fuck yeah!
我就会推倒她
I'd be all over that.
我想... 我他妈会...
I'd, like... I'd fuckin'...
操
Fuck.
好吧 那...
OK, well...
我需要一点东西 你有薄荷糖吗
I need something. Do you have a Smint?
-什么  -你有薄荷糖吗
- What? - Do you have a Smint?
没有 直接攥着你的大香肠上吧
No! Just grab your baloney-pipe and jizz.
-好吧 好吧  -对的
- OK. OK. - Yeah. OK.
要香槟吗
Champagne?
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
你得进公关部门
You gotta get into P.R.
那他妈才是真金白银去的...
That's where the real fuckin' money...
你觉得现在是
Do you think now would be
和老蠢货谈谈的好时机吗
a good time to sit down with the old fart?
哥们 你刚看到有个人在点心拼盘边上打飞机了吗
Dude, did you see that guy jerking off near the hors d'oeuvres?
哥们 那真他妈是健康警报
Dude, that's a fuckin' health hazard.
不是 你觉得我多久能跟他谈
No. When do you think I can talk to him?
我真的很想得到一些能带回去的消息
I'd really love to hear something to take home.
小罗罗 你他妈能淡定点吗 伙计
Ro-Ro, can you just be fucking cool, man?
去吃个迷你汉堡
Maybe get a slider.
问问有没有人愿意被你爆菊 好吗 哥们
Ask if you can stick your finger up someone's ass, all right, buddy?
-天呐  -那谁 操你妈
- Jeez. - Hey! Fuck you!
我不是你可以随意摆弄的小宠物
I'm not your little pet that you get to kick around.
对不起 不好意思 穿宇宙服的大哥
Oh, I'm sorry. Excuse me, space suit.
兄弟
Bro.
你以为我没法子搞惨你
You think that I can't make your life difficult,
但只要我跟某些人说一声
but word in the right ear,
我能让你很头疼 混账东西
and I could be your migraine, motherfucker.
我来这是为了和老头子谈谈 这是你答应的
I came here to talk to the old man on your word,
所以给我做到
so make it happen.
-行  -是吗
- OK. - Yeah?
-可以  -好
- All right. - Cool.
我想躲... 但它会找到你
I tried to hide... but it finds you.
不管你躲在哪 这派对总能找到你
Wherever you hide, the party finds you.
先生 这是你最后一次警告
Sir, this is your final warning.
绝对的
Absolutely.
我明白
Got it.
等等 发生了什么
Wait. What's happening?
你这位朋友
Your friend here
一直告诉别人他爱上了他们
keeps telling people he's in love with them,
让别人很不舒服
and it's making people uncomfortable.
我的错 信号太混乱了
My bad. Mixed messages.
只是我们都对肠道细菌有很强的同感[接吻]
It's just we share such strong feelings about gut bacteria
我觉得我理解错了
I think I got the wrong end of the stick.
盯着他
Watch him.
也许我该去道个歉
Maybe I should go apologize.
抱一下她
Give her a hug.
我的天 兄弟
My God, dude!
刚才太疯狂了
That was insane!
-是吗  -对啊 我跟这个姑娘
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah. Me and this girl,
我们进了个侧间 开始亲热
we go into this side room and we start making out,
然后我开始摸她
and then I'm touching her
接着她给我口交
and then she goes down on me,
后来我射在了她嘴里 然后...
and then I splooge in her mouth, and...
牛吧 牛吧
I know! I know!
重点来了 她亲了我
And get this. She kisses me
把它吐回我嘴里 然后我吞了下去
and puts it back in my mouth, and I swallow.
什么 精液吗
Which, the cum?
对 太火辣了
I know. So hot!
你吞了自己的精液
You swallowed your own load?
对啊 我听说过 但我不...
Yeah. I heard of it, but I don't...
我不知道它会发生
I didn't know it actually happened.
我以前没听说过
I haven't heard about it before.
我听说过 有这种事 有关于这的传言
I have. It's a thing. There's a word for it.
我现在不记得是怎么说的了
I can't remember what it is right now.
太他妈火辣了
So fuckin' hot.
我们多久能回家
When are we allowed to go home?
车五点来接我们
We have cars at 5:00.
格雷格 这是我生命中最美好的时光
Greg, I'm having the time of my life.
真像一场噩梦
This is nightmarish.
你准备好开始单身派对了吗
You ready for your bachelorette party?
他们的海军制服租完了
They were out of marine uniforms,
所以我乔装成了政治顾问
so I've come dressed as a political consultant.
那...
Sss...
放松
Relax.
这关系并不正经
This isn't real.
它正在变得正经 而且也许会对我们有弊
It's becoming real, which might be a problem for us.
我能留下吗
Uh... can I stay?
但你只能当忠犬
But with you, as a human dog
躺在床尾好吗
just at the foot of the bed?
我爱你 小肯
I love you, Kenny.
-我也爱你 老哥  -我想找到那个姑娘
- I love you too, man. - I'm tryin' to find this girl,
但她应该在躲我
but I think she's trying to hide from me.
那啥 还有用来乱搞的别的房间吗
Listen, is there another room for humping?
因为我也找不到罗曼了
'Cause I also lost Roman.
-别管罗曼了  -你知道
- Fuck Roman. - Well, you know,
他在问狗笼的事
he was askin' about the dog pound,
好像有点生气
and he got kind of riled up.
他还在说那事吗
Is he still talking about that?
对
Yeah.
-真可悲  -是啊
- It's pathetic. - Yeah.
他乐在其中 对吧
He enjoyed it, right?
当然
Oh, yeah!
你也很享受
I mean, you did too.
就胡闹着玩玩呗
You know, just messin' around.
对啊 胡闹
Yeah, just messin' around.
爸的原则是如果你有两只斗犬
Dad's theory was you got two fighting dogs,
送走那只软弱的
you send the weak one away,
惩罚软弱的那只
you punish the weak one.
这样大家都知道等级如何
Then everyone knows the hierarchy,
皆大欢喜
then everyone's happy.
所以他就被送走了
So away he went.
我得再去找了
I gotta keep lookin'. OK.
晚上好 请问
Hi! Hey, may I ask you,
911的时候你在哪儿
where were you on 9/11?
我... 算了
You know what, I... Never mind.
听着 桑迪
Listen, Sandy.
我很欣赏你的提议 但我不会退出
I appreciate your offer. I'm not getting out.
那好吧 如果你觉得
OK. Well, if you think you
非要给你爸打小报告 再回去给他办事
have to tell your father and get back in with him,
-那我就...  -留着你的钱
- then I... - Keep your money.
留着你的钱 拉我进去
Keep your money, bring me in.
我们得体地办好这事
We do this properly.
咱们一起搞死我爸
We'll go fuck my dad together.
接手大权
Takeover.
杠杆收购 恶意的
Leveraged buyout. Hostile.
杠杆收购: 公司或个体利用收购目标的资产作为债务抵押收购此公司
这可是双重股权局面
That's a dual stock situation.
双重股权: 通过分离现金流和控制权 对公司实行有效控制
不可能坦率的
That's not gonna be straightforward.
股价跌到谷底 股东们都气疯了...
Price in the toilet, shareholders are pissed...
你和我能逼他上谈判桌
you and me could force him to the table.
那你其他家人怎么办
What about the rest of your family?
管他妈什么家人
Fuck the rest of my family.
-说得轻巧  -没人比我更懂
- Easy to say. - No one has a clue but me.
我知道该怎么办 看得清清楚楚
I know what to do. I see it all.
咱们能拆散它
We take it apart.
本地电视台 报纸和公园全滚蛋...
Fuck local TV, newspapers, parks...
我们他妈的威胁整个贫民区
we bulldoze the whole fuckin' shantytown.
只需要保持可口的口水话信息
We just keep the juiciest morsels,
把一群腐烂的鲸鱼转变为
turn the thing from a pod of rotting whales
一头大白鲨老大
into one bastard great white.
你的目标是什么
What's your end?
上任总裁 我是唯一了解架构的人
CEO. I'm the only one who knows the architecture.
懂吗 情感化的企业架构
OK? The emotional corporate architecture.
我没问题 但斯图伊可能不同意
Well, I could like it. Stewy might not like it.
滚他妈的斯图伊
Fuck Stewy.
斯图伊会像一条卡通狗被钱钓着走
Stewy will follow the money like a dog in a cartoon.
你确定自己胃口有这么大
And you sure you got the stomach?
当然
Yeah.
我很好
I'm good.
汤姆
Tom.
...抱歉吵醒你
...sorry to wake you.
你好 出事了吗
Hey. Is everything OK?
没有
No.
他呼吸有点不通畅
He couldn't catch his breath.
听我说 这是医生的建议 对此我们非常抱歉
Listen, we've been advised, and we are really sorry,
但我觉得
but I don't think it's a
他去参加婚礼不是个好主意
good idea for him to come to the wedding.
好吧 听着很合理
Oh, yeah. That sounds sensible.
小西
Shiv.
他真的很抱歉
He really is sorry.
当然 我也是
Yeah, me too.
行 再见
OK, bye.
你没事吧
You OK?
当然 我很好 少了两位宾客
Yeah. I'm great. That's two less wedding dinners
宴席筹办商又轻松了
for the caterers to have to organize.
搞不懂 纳特
I don't know, Nate.
真他妈搞不懂
I don't fuckin' know.
我会做你的先遣兵
And I would be your point man on this,
这样你就不用和我爸正面交锋
so you would not have to deal direct with my dad.
如果我们能达成一个价格...
So if we can find a price...
-很有可能对吧  -没准呢
- But there's potential? - It could happen.
那行 真激动人心
Well, fuck, I'm excited.
还不错 情况很阳光
This is great. This is pure upside.
-谢谢  -太棒了 兄弟
- Thank you. - Awesome, dude.
咱们逗他玩会儿
Let's jerk him around for a bit,
再拒绝他
then throw him back.
什么破家族
This fuckin' family.
等下 等等
Ooh, hey! Come on.
情况如何
How's it goin'?
干嘛
What?
你想看穿我吗
What, are you psyching me out?
我好怕怕哦
I'm fuckin' terrified.
混蛋
Asshole!
靠
Shit.
如果车再不来
If the car doesn't come soon,
我可能就要游回家了
I'm just gonna swim home, I think.
格雷格跟我说你把自个儿精液吞了
Greg tells me you swallowed your own load.
对 那时... 那时候很疯狂
Yeah, It was... Yeah. It was pretty wild.
但是还不赖 因为这样我就没出轨
It's cool, though, 'cause it's like I didn't cheat
因为所有精子都还在体内
'cause all the sperm stayed in my own body.
就像个封闭的循坏系统...
Like a closed loop system. So...
真想快点回去见小西
It'd be really nice to see Shiv.
威拉 亲爱的 我只想说我爱你
Willa! Hi, I just want to say I love you.
我非常爱你
I love you so much.
怎么回事 车去哪儿了
What's happening? Where's the car?
五点就来
Arriving in five.
祝贺你 汤姆
Congratulations, Tom.
我听说你把自个儿精液吞了
I hear you swallowed your own load.
对 是的
Yeah, I did.
今晚特别开心
It's been a really wonderful night.
我当然想吃鸡肉派
I would love a chicken pot pie.
谢谢你
Thank you.
好 宝贝 再见
OK, honey, bye.
小西
Hey, Shiv!
我回来了
I'm home!
我的眼球都还在呢
Still got both my eyebrows!
-你好  -你好
- Oh, hi! - Hey.
你都回来了... 这么快
Hey, you're back... already.
老天 我好想你 宝贝 太想你了
God, I missed you, honey. God, I missed you.
-我也想你  -感觉怎么样
- I missed you. - How was it?
-什么... 派对吗  -对啊
- Which... Oh, the party? - Yeah.
可开心了
It was a blast.
-是吗  -是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
那... 发生了些什么
So... what happened?
你知道的 就是...
You know, just...
这样那样的
like, this and that.
通常 正常的事
Usual. Normal stuff.
具体是什么 汤姆
Specifically what, Tom?
等下 什么意思 别啊 小西 你...
Wait, what? No. Shiv, you...
我以为你说...
I thought you said...
亲爱的 我逗你玩呢
Oh, honey, I'm shitting you.
老天啊 好吧
Oh, my God, OK.
你回来了我很高兴
Oh, it's good to have you back.
喂 弗兰克
Yeah, Frank.
搞艺术那些姑娘
Those girls from the art thing,
我要你放出话说她们是瘾君子
I want you to put the word around they're junkies,
是贱货 种子资金都被她们换毒品
they're sluts, they're shooting seed capital
直接注射进手臂了
straight into their arms.
搞臭她们
Let's sink them.
先生们 开始吧
Gentlemen. Shall we?
真不愧是我兄弟
My man.
THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠